export default {
  id: 'addition',
  type: 'interview',
  attributes: {
    operator: '+',
    questions: [
      {
        prompt: '5 + 1',
        answer: 6,
        column: 1,
      },
      {
        prompt: '1 + 7',
        answer: 8,
        column: 1,
      },
      {
        prompt: '1 + 9',
        answer: 10,
        column: 1,
      },
      {
        prompt: '4 + 2',
        answer: 6,
        column: 1,
      },
      {
        prompt: '2 + 5',
        answer: 7,
        column: 1,
      },
      {
        prompt: '3 + 2',
        answer: 5,
        column: 1,
      },
      {
        prompt: '2 + 4',
        answer: 6,
        column: 1,
      },
      {
        prompt: '2 + 6',
        answer: 8,
        column: 1,
      },
      {
        prompt: '2 + 3',
        answer: 5,
        column: 1,
      },
      {
        prompt: '2 + 7',
        answer: 9,
        column: 1,
      },
      {
        prompt: '3 + 3',
        answer: 6,
        column: 2,
      },
      {
        prompt: '3 + 4',
        answer: 7,
        column: 2,
      },
      {
        prompt: '3 + 6',
        answer: 9,
        column: 2,
      },
      {
        prompt: '0 + 9',
        answer: 9,
        column: 2,
      },
      {
        prompt: '3 + 5',
        answer: 8,
        column: 2,
      },
      {
        prompt: '4 + 4',
        answer: 8,
        column: 2,
      },
      {
        prompt: '5 + 3',
        answer: 8,
        column: 2,
      },
      {
        prompt: '4 + 3',
        answer: 7,
        column: 2,
      },
      {
        prompt: '4 + 5',
        answer: 9,
        column: 2,
      },
      {
        prompt: '6 + 4',
        answer: 10,
        column: 2,
      },
      {
        prompt: '4 + 6',
        answer: 10,
        column: 3,
      },
      {
        prompt: '5 + 5',
        answer: 10,
        column: 3,
      },
      {
        prompt: '3 + 7',
        answer: 10,
        column: 3,
      },
      {
        prompt: '2 + 8',
        answer: 10,
        column: 3,
      },
      {
        prompt: '6 + 6',
        answer: 12,
        column: 3,
      },
      {
        prompt: '2 + 9',
        answer: 11,
        column: 3,
      },
      {
        prompt: '7 + 4',
        answer: 11,
        column: 3,
      },
      {
        prompt: '5 + 6',
        answer: 11,
        column: 3,
      },
      {
        prompt: '3 + 8',
        answer: 11,
        column: 3,
      },
      {
        prompt: '7 + 5',
        answer: 12,
        column: 3,
      },
      {
        prompt: '6 + 8',
        answer: 14,
        column: 4,
      },
      {
        prompt: '3 + 9',
        answer: 12,
        column: 4,
      },
      {
        prompt: '9 + 3',
        answer: 12,
        column: 4,
      },
      {
        prompt: '8 + 7',
        answer: 15,
        column: 4,
      },
      {
        prompt: '7 + 7',
        answer: 14,
        column: 4,
      },
      {
        prompt: '6 + 7',
        answer: 13,
        column: 4,
      },
      {
        prompt: '7 + 9',
        answer: 16,
        column: 4,
      },
      {
        prompt: '9 + 8',
        answer: 17,
        column: 4,
      },
      {
        prompt: '8 + 8',
        answer: 16,
        column: 4,
      },
      {
        prompt: '8 + 5',
        answer: 13,
        column: 4,
      },
      {
        prompt: '5 + 7',
        answer: 12,
        column: 5,
      },
      {
        prompt: '5 + 9',
        answer: 14,
        column: 5,
      },
      {
        prompt: '8 + 6',
        answer: 14,
        column: 5,
      },
      {
        prompt: '9 + 9',
        answer: 18,
        column: 5,
      },
      {
        prompt: '4 + 9',
        answer: 13,
        column: 5,
      },
      {
        prompt: '8 + 4',
        answer: 12,
        column: 5,
      },
      {
        prompt: '6 + 9',
        answer: 15,
        column: 5,
      },
      {
        prompt: '7 + 8',
        answer: 15,
        column: 5,
      },
      {
        prompt: '9 + 7',
        answer: 16,
        column: 5,
      },
      {
        prompt: '5 + 8',
        answer: 13,
        column: 5,
      },
    ],
  },
};
